const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '703 − 185 =', answer: '518', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '907 − 689 =', answer: '218', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '908 − 599 =', answer: '309', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '803 − 384 =', answer: '419', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '804 − 257 =', answer: '547', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '602 − 184 =', answer: '418', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '903 − 185 =', answer: '718', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '905 − 367 =', answer: '538', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '807 − 458 =', answer: '349', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '703 − 285 =', answer: '418', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];